giftstoindia24x7.com 2019-04-11

# Giftstoindia24x7.com :: Privacy Policy.

  * What information does GiftsToIndia24x7.com collect about me?

GiftsToIndia24x7.com is an online e-commerce website designed to provide an easy way for our customers to shop online. GiftsToIndia24x7.com’s customers fill in details with regards to their billing address and the details of where the gifts are going to be shipped to. We also collect IP address when the customer transacts on GiftsToIndia24x7.com. None of the information we gather can be used by the public (visitors, other members, and anyone not employed by GiftsToIndia24x7.com., its corporate affiliates, or the financial institutions we use to process credit cards) to identify a specific individual.

  * What does GiftsToIndia24x7.com do with the information it collects?

GiftsToIndia24x7.com uses the information it collects in the following ways.

E-mail addresses submitted by members are used by us when sending newsletters. E-mail addresses may also be used in private correspondence with the user for customer service issues. All other private information submitted by the user is confidential and will not be disclosed except as required by law or to protect members of GiftsToIndia24x7.com.

Information that users do not submit to GiftsToIndia24x7.com: We use your server, IP address, and browser-type related information in the general management of GiftsToIndia24x7.com and fraud protection.

Service Providers

We use other third parties to provide logistics and payment processing on our site. When you transact or place an order on our site, we will share shipping address with the logistics provider as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

  * With whom does GiftsToIndia24x7.com share the information it collects?

We do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your private information without your permission except to the financial institution that processes your credit card transactions. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

  * How can I change or update my Personal Information?

You can change the information by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

Telephone Contact Number:  
India : +91.933.953.0030 

Postal Address:  
GiftsToIndia24x7.com  
76, B. B. Ganguly Street,  
Ground Floor  
Kolkata – 700012 

  * Tell me about Cookies

giftstoindia24x7.com uses cookies to deliver the various services and to keep track of your personal preference. A cookie is a small text file that can be entered into the memory of your browser to help a web site recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behaviour and compile aggregate data that allows Internet services to make content improvements and targeted advertising.

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, most browsers contain a function that allows a user to deny the cookie feature. You can also delete cookie files from your computer at your discretion. Please note that the use of cookies is a necessary part of the giftstoindia24x7.com technology and are necessary if you wish to access giftstoindia24x7.com. Disabling the cookie feature on your browser or deleting cookie files from your computer will render you unable to access certain features on giftstoindia24x7.com and participate in its services. Cookies may also be necessary to provide the user with certain features such as customized delivery of information.

giftstoindia24x7.com uses cookies to provide the services, to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes. Please note that cookies are used only to recollect information sent to your computer from giftstoindia24x7.com.com. We CANNOT access any information not sent by giftstoindia24x7.com. We also do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. Third Party Cookies : Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by R G Cards.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

  * Customer Reviews and Testimonials.

GiftsToIndia24x7.com allows customer to review its product listing. This service is not compulsory and its user’s option to submit a review. In case a user wants their review / testimonial to be removed, he / She can write to customer support at sales@giftstoindia24x7.com for removal of his / her review.

  * Changes in the privacy statement.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
